### **KEERBI LIU**

2/16 Raine Road Padstow NSW 2211

Kirby.liu12@gmail.com (H) 02 9792 3826 (M) 0410 967 990

# **Background**

Currently an undergraduate student at the University of Technology Sydney, studying engineering with a major in mechanical and mechatronics. Six months of experience working in the fast food industry and currently employed in hospitality and entertainment.

### Qualifications

Valid until 28/12/2020 Current NSW class CP2 drivers licence.

Valid until 28/01/2022 Competency card in the Responsible Service of Alcohol. (RSA)

Valid until 28/01/2022 Competency card in the Responsible Conduct of Gambling.

(RCG)

### Education

3/2017 – Current University of Technology Sydney (UTS)

Undertaking a Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) Bachelor of

Science.

1/2010 – 10/2016 Hurlstone Agricultural High School (HAHS)

Majored in engineering studies, received an award for academic

excellence in engineering.

Received an award for service to Hurlstone sound and lighting.

## **Work Experience**

11/2016 – 6/2017 Hungry Jacks, as a cafe worker, responsibilities include: the

cooking and handling of food through correct health and safety

procedures.

**7/2017 – Current** Zone Bowling Revesby, as a Party Host, Café attendant.

Responsibilities include: Knowledge in correct cash handling, correct manual handling procedures, as well as the responsible

service of alcohol.

### Skills

#### **Excellent social and communication skills**

Actively participated and volunteered in many extra-curricular activities at HAHS, such as the HAHS country fair, fundraiser Barbeques and musical productions. Gained experience in communication from working at Zone Revesby as a party host and food attendant, due to the many upfront interactions with customers and guests.

### Strong organisation skills

Living in the boarding school, meant a tight schedule in managing time for family, academics and Leisure. The position of a party host at Zone Bowling Revesby, included responsibilities such as, good organisation to ensure the party runs smoothly and efficiently.

### Good adaptability skills

Previously worked in the fast food industry for Hungry Jacks and have adapted to working in a high-pressure environment. Able to learn quickly and micromanage tasks extremely well. Have been trained to keep a professional appearance at all times, through training at Zone Bowling Revesby.

### Technical and manual skills

Part of the HAHS sound and lighting for five years and gained experience in the managing and setup of audio and lighting devices used in stage performances, such as microphones speakers and programable lighting. Helped setup for school socials, school assemblies and School musicals. Trained in the manual handling of heavy equipment and objects.

Well trained in the use of Microsoft Excel as a medium for data analysis, and formatting.

### Referee

(H) 02 9829 9232 <a href="mailto:hurlstone-h.school@det.nsw.edu.au">hurlstone-h.school@det.nsw.edu.au</a>, Boarding school administration.

(M) 0414 015 072 Damian Geerling, Boarding head teacher welfare.

(M) 0412 130 491 Nicki Kaplanis, Venue Manager at Zone Bowling Revesby.

(W) 02 9793 2374 Hungry Jacks Bankstown, manager Ahmed.